smokeybones.com 2008-06-17

# Smokey Bones Barbeque and Grill Privacy Policy

**Effective Date: October 1, 2004**

**SMOKEY BONES PRIVACY POLICY**

Smokey Bones respects the privacy of every individual who visits our website. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. **By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.**

**If you visit our website:**  
In general, you can visit our website without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. Our web servers collect the domain names, not the e-mail addresses, of visitors. 

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. This information is collected using a "cookie" that enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. Cookies are small files placed on your hard drive that allow us to collect that information. Smokey Bones, along with our ad management partner, DoubleClick, uses this information to help us manage online advertising. None of the information collected by a cookie is personally identifiable, i.e., does not contain your name, address or e-mail address. For more information about DoubleClick, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, go to [http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy ](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy). 

Smokey Bones also utilizes a third party to track and analyze usage and volume statistical information from our website customers in order to constantly improve the quality of our website. No data collected by a third party on behalf of Smokey Bones may be owned or used by such third party. Smokey Bones reserves the right to publish nonpersonally identifiable, summary information regarding its website customers for promotional purposes and as a representative audience for advertisers. 

**If you choose to identify yourself:**  
If you voluntarily provide us with personally identifying information, such as your name, street address, email address, phone number, and birth date, we will collect that information along with any other information you voluntarily provide. 

It is our policy not to distribute, sell, rent or in any way make available, your name, e-mail address or any other personally identifiable information to any third party. 

When you participate in site features such as newsletters, sweepstakes, recipe sharing, fresh to your door, etc., we may use the personally identifiable information you provide through those features in the following ways, unless stated otherwise: 

  * we may store and process that information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services, and 
  * we may communicate with you via e-mail or postal mail. 

**Deletion of Personal Information**  
If at any time you do not wish to have your personal information collected, you may cancel your membership through our website. You may access, update, or cancel your membership on our website at any time. Upon cancellation, all of your personal information will be deleted from our system. 

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act**  
Smokey Bones has no intention of collecting any personally identifiable information (name, address, telephone number, birth date, or e-mail address) from individuals under 13 years of age. If a child has provided us with personally identifiable information, a parent or guardian of that child should contact us at the e-mail address or phone number listed at the bottom of this Statement if they would like this information deleted from our records. We will use reasonable efforts to delete the child's information from our existing files. 

**Policy Changes**  
Smokey Bones may, at any time, amend the provisions in this Privacy Policy. Changes to this policy will be reflected by the "Effective Date" as displayed in the upper left hand corner of this policy. 

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or use of your information, please contact us at: [feedback@smokeybones.com ](mailto:feedback@smokeybones.com) or by mail at 

Smokey Bones   
P.O. Box 593330   
Orlando, FL 32859-3330
